It's my first day of freshman year.
Oh my god. But it's my first day of
freshman year. Don't play. Don't play.
Good morning, y'all. It's my first day
of sophomore year. Like I'm actually
excited. Good morning. It's my first day
of junior year. Y'all, it is my first
day of senior year. I'm so excited.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Good morning. First day of senior year.
Oh my gosh.
Y'all, it is my first day of senior
year. I'm so excited. Like I'm literally
so excited. This is my last first day.
Like that is insane. Because I literally
remember freshman year. Like I remember
getting ready for my first day of
freshman year. Like that is insane, bro.
Time flies by so fast. When they tell
y'all that high school flies by fast,
listen cuz it really does. It really
really does. Like I'm a whole senior
now. That is crazy. But anyways, it is
currently 5:00 in the morning and
I did have an alarm, but
I was already up, so my alarm didn't
like ring cuz I was already on my phone.
It did ring, but it rang like as a
notification if that makes sense. So I
couldn't really record my alarm ringing.
I've been up for an hour now. So I've
been up since 4:00 a.m. I kid you not
because I was transferring footage
from my SD card. If y'all can't tell
already, I am a morning person. Like I
actually be thriving in the morning.
Like I'm up. 4:00 a.m. 5:00 a.m. I'm up.
I never cared. Like I literally am the
biggest morning person you will ever
meet. I feel like I'm not really a night
person. Like, when it's night time,
y'all, I'm ready to go to sleep, for
real. I'm finna go to the bathroom, do
my hygiene routine, y'all know the
drill, so, yeah.
>> [music]
[music]
>> All right, guys, so, I finished doing my
oral hygiene and my skin care. I
literally only use one cleanser to wash
my face. My skin care routine is not
really complicated. But, yeah, I use the
La Roche-Posay hydrating gentle
cleanser.
>> [snorts]
>> But, I'm about to hop in the shower. I'm
going to show you guys what I'm going to
use. The only thing I'm not going to
show you guys is my Dove bar soap. I
will be using Dove bar soap. I'm not
going to show y'all cuz it's literally
like like I'm using like a little bit of
the bar soap left. So, it's not really
going to like look aesthetic in the
video, if that makes sense. But, I'm
going to show y'all the rest of the
products I'm going to be using for my
body.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Cuz I love
>> Hey y'all, so I got out the shower. It
is now 5:54. Well, I've been out the
shower, but I was like setting up my
camera. I had to get my robe. My skin is
so dry right now. Like I have really dry
skin. So, I'm going to quickly
moisturize it. I do want to say I feel
like I got to say this in every video.
The reason why I'm missing a nail on my
pinky is because I didn't get my pinky
done when I was going to get my nails
done because I got my pinky damaged.
Y'all be watching thinking I'm missing a
nail like it fell off or something, but
I just never got this finger done.
But anyways, I'm about to use the Anua
Hold on, let me show you guys.
To moisturize my face, I'm using the
Anua moisturizing milk. Honestly, I
don't know how to feel about like it
being my first day of senior year. I
feel like it's bittersweet. Like I'm
excited, but at the same time it's kind
of like, "Oh my gosh, school's starting
again." But then again, I'm like, "Wait,
no. This is my last first day." And then
I'm also like, "Oh my gosh, thank god.
This is my last first day." Like I don't
know how to feel. It's just My emotions
are all over the place, bro. I'm going
to put Vaseline
Using some Vaseline after I use this.
Moisturize my neck and my face. So, now
I'm going to moisturize the rest of my
body. Let me show you guys. So, I have
two
Okay.
I'm a little clumsy, y'all.
Just a little bit.
I don't know why
Okay, let me not say that out loud cuz
that's lowkey TMI.
Anyways, for lotion, I got the
pomegranate raspberry and the fresh and
cozy lotion. They're both new bottles of
lotion. I think I'm going to use fresh
and cozy cuz I did use the scented body
wash
as my last wash in the shower.
Oop.
The way that it popped just like threw
me off. This scent right here gives very
much clean girl. Like it smells super
good. It smells like fresh laundry.
Y'all, this be taking forever. Like
Finally. For my whole body, I don't just
use EOS lotion. I also use Vaseline. So,
I kind of mix it, but I don't put EOS
lotion on my face, y'all. Like at all. I
just put some Vaseline on my palm as
well as some EOS lotion and I mix it
together.
And then I use it to moisturize my whole
body. I'm going to be right back cuz I'm
about to take my robe off and moisturize
my full body off camera
and then I'll be right back. All right,
y'all. So, my whole body is moisturized.
Also guys, I did use this. This is the
Palmer's body oil. The whole bottle is
submerged in oil literally. By the way,
this robe is by Juicy Couture. It is so
cute. Like it has Juicy Couture right
here and it also has it in the back.
Hold on, let me show y'all.
All right, y'all. That's basically it
for this part of my get ready with me.
I'm going to go show you guys what I'm
going to wear for school
and then we're going to put it on and
then we're going to start on my hair.
Y'all
I was really debating if I wanted to do
my makeup, but I'm not going to. I was
on the phone with my friends and they
were asking if I was going to do my
makeup, but I was like, "No."
And they were like, "What?" For those
who have been watching like my more
recent videos, you know that I recently,
you know, just started learning how to
do my own makeup. I went to Ulta and I
got a bunch of makeup products. So,
yeah. I literally just started learning
how to do my makeup. I don't really wear
makeup on a daily, but recently
especially this summer, I've been
wearing it every time I get the chance
to especially when I'm going out with my
friends just to practice because I feel
like the more you practice, the more you
get the hang of it. I don't think I want
to do my makeup for the first day of
senior year. Like I think I want to go
bare face and maybe I'll wear it for the
second day of school. I'm just going to
go bare face because yeah.
But, I'm going to show you guys um
my clothes. All right, guys. This is my
outfit. Super cute. Like I'm really
pinked out. So, I got this True Religion
hoodie. It's a cream on the socks, but I
got this Marc Jacobs bag. So cute. For
shoes, I'm wearing my Speed Cats. The
color of my bag and shoes match pretty
well. They're not identical, but they're
very similar. And I also have this tank
top that I'm going to wear under the
hoodie. So, yeah, y'all. This is my
outfit. Real pink. Real cute. Let me put
the box to the side. But, yeah. Let me
show y'all the back of the hoodie cuz
this is real cute.
This is the back of the hoodie, y'all.
This is so fire. Like, I love it so
much. It's so cute. The rhinestones.
Like, hello. The detailing is just
really good. True Religion all in
rhinestones and it has this bow. This is
so cute. Like, I literally love the back
so much.
So cute. All right, y'all. So, I'm now
fully dressed and I'm about to start on
my hair.
So,
this is what we got to work with. I
wrapped everything just so I can
maintain a part. Really? Let me take
this off. All right, y'all. Ignore what
we got going on right here. I'm about to
take this out.
Okay.
And then,
this part.
I poured water in this bottle. It says
primer water. Y'all, there's no primer
in here. It's like a old makeup product,
I'm pretty sure. I just use the spray
bottle now and it's just water in here.
I did put some of the Eden lip gloss on,
y'all. I'm still going to do my lip
combo by the way. I don't want my lips
to be dry
while
I'm getting ready.
>> [music]
>> All right, y'all. So, my hair is done. I
sprayed some water to like make the
curls pop a little bit more. Oh, for
edge control I used the gummy wax as
control.
Just to like touch the edges up a little
bit. So now I'm about to do my lip
combo.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I used a little bit of the Eos lip gloss
and I used some of the Broadway lip
gloss as well.
But
yeah, I'm not going to lie y'all, my
school is getting way stricter on
electronics. Like they're literally
being at school. We can't have phones
throughout the whole school day. Last
school year we couldn't have our phones
in class, but we could have them at
lunch and in the hallway, but this
school year y'all we can't even have
them at lunch or in the hallway. This is
the first year they're like implementing
the ban, so I want to see how that's
going to work out. But yeah, I'm still
going to bring my AirPods with me. Like
I still can't believe we cannot use
anything. Like no headphones or
anything. Even at lunch. Like lunch is
really what's blowing me. I understand
not having our phones in class, like
while class is in session, that's
understandable. But what do you mean in
the hallway and during lunch? Like what?
Anyways,
I charged all my devices last night.
It's now 7:00 on the dot, y'all.
I'm about to put my watch on.
I'm actually a little nervous. Oh my
gosh.
Also y'all I did put deodorant on. I
used the Dove sheer cool deodorant. I
just didn't get to film me putting it
on, but just wanted to put
[clears throat] that out there. Y'all
this is actually the first school year
that I have a skirt on for the first day
of school, cuz I know my freshman year I
wore jeans.
Sophomore year I wore jeans, like long
jeans. And um junior I also wore long
jeans. So this is my first year wearing
a skirt. Anyways,
what else?
Y'all we're supposed to get our IDs
today, like new school IDs,
but I'm going to take the one I had from
junior year with me.
Even though I probably don't really need
it for real,
cuz I should be getting a new one
today.
But yeah, we're pretty much ready. Time
check, it's now 7:03. Let me shorten the
strap for this, cuz I'm going to wear it
like on the shoulder, kind of.
Like that, instead of crossbody. So,
this is my tote bag. Y'all, this is my
actual book bag for school. It's this
Coach bag, and it is so cute. Like I
love this bag so much, but I'm not going
to be using it on the first day. I'm
actually going to be wearing my senior
backpack, cuz like it's the first day of
senior year, so I feel like it makes
sense. I have my school supplies in
here, so this bag is a little heavy.
This is my senior backpack, y'all. It's
a strawberry shortcake bag. So, y'all,
this is my bag. So, all right, y'all, so
this is my outfit. I got the True
Religion jacket. My tank top is from
Fashion Nova. The skirt is from Fashion
Nova. And then I got my pink Puma
Speedcats with my Supreme socks. But
this is how my outfit is looking.
All right, y'all, so I am at school. I
actually came a little too early. I had
to have a teacher open the door for me,
and I'm actually in his classroom right
now, because he let me come in here. The
bell is going to ring in like
Apparently, the bell is supposed to ring
right now, 8:05.
So, I actually might get up and leave
now, cuz he told me once it's 8:05, I
can go. So, yeah, we're supposed to go
into like our SRT. SRT is basically like
home room.
But we call it SRT at my school. So, I'm
supposed to go in there to get my
schedule. I have my schedule, but
they're going to give us another copy
and our ID. They actually completely
changed how the IDs look, y'all.
>> Yes, can we all
>> Yes, we got
>> Wait.
>> Our phones are way at 8:25. So, like in
the morning, you can
>> Oh, oh, really?
Oh, okay.
>> It's like bell FOR BELL.
>> OH, GUYS, I'M SO SAD. This is Harmony.
>> Hello, guys.
>> Y'all, you guys did Welcome to the first
day OF SCHOOL, GUYS.
>> IT'S THE FIRST day of my junior year of
high school. I'm so excited. I'm going
to look for all the FRESHMAN HIGH
SCHOOL.
>> [screaming]
[laughter]
>> SORRY. OKAY.
WHERE? WHERE? GUYS.
OKAY, GUYS. Y'ALL [laughter] WERE
LOOKING FOR THE freshman high school all
summer.
Oh, yes. Literally pinked out. Pinked
out. I don't even think you knew. We
were all wearing pink cuz pink was
senior color.
>> Aw, pink.
>> Hi Mr. Clark.
>> Hey, how are you?
>> Good. How are you?
>> GOOD.
>> OH, IF YOU DON'T PUT YOUR PHONE THIS
like A25, then you're going to blow you
up.
>> No, but really I actually like the
outline of the phone, too. Like you get
in trouble.
>> Really?
>> What?
HONESTLY, LIKE I THINK I'LL SURVIVE. I'm
just
>> You look so cute.
>> have upstairs at all?
>> Yeah.
>> Do you have him?
>> He's so good. I actually [laughter]
TEXTED YOU ABOUT IT.
>> OH, YOU DID?
>> YEAH. AS Y'ALL CAN SEE, they're yapping
away. Like it's like we haven't talked
in forever.
>> Because we haven't.
>> We really have.
>> 8:22, we need to be in classrooms in 3
minutes.
>> Where's your senior backpack?
>> Literally, mine is in my classroom. Um,
I'm so excited for the school year and
I'm so excited to be a senior and
graduate and leave this.
>> ME, TOO.
>> UM, I'M GOING TO CRY A LOT CUZ ALL MY
FRIENDS ARE GRADUATING, TOO. That's how
I feel. [laughter]
>> She's a junior, guys.
>> No,
I have to stay for this full experience.
And you guys better go on a senior trip
and better take cute Instagram pictures.
>> We will.
>> Okay.
>> How do you turn them in?
>> All right. I know y'all missed me. Like
y'all haven't seen me since June.
I'm cute.
Anyway.
Boom, Amir. Freak.
>> You are cute.
>> I KNOW. OKAY.
>> GIRL.
>> AMIR is cute.
>> Oh, sorry. Thank you. Can you take your
schedule out my hand? I look like a
loser walking around with
>> Y'all know.
I GOT
I'M True Religion down.
>> HEY PAUL,
AND SMALL LITTLE SHIRT. THESE pants and
these shoes are FROM
>> HURRY UP.
>> AND my shoes JD and in my tank top I
don't know and in my purse.
>> Here is tea.
>> Thank you.
>> You know THE QUEEN IS BACK WITH IT.
>> MY SHIRT I GOT IT FROM AMAZON skirt from
Shein.
And then I got my ASICS so yeah.
>> Oh you're OVERLY ENERGETIC TODAY.
>> WE'RE GOING TO GO GET LUNCH. WELL I'M
NOT GETTING LUNCH cuz I don't think I
like what they have but
Yeah totally.
>> Yeah.
>> You kind OF LOOK LIKE JURO.
>> [laughter]
>> GUYS WHY ARE WE
>> WE'RE LOSERS BRO.
>> SHE HUNGRY AS
>> NOBODY'S IN MY HOUSE.
>> I HAVE I HAVE A CAR.
>> HEY.
>> OKAY HI BYE.
>> WAIT.
>> MAKE MAKE EDITS OF US.
>> GO FOR ALL.
>> BYE GUYS.
>> GUYS THIS IS THE BUBBLE TRIO.
>> KISS ME.
KISS ME.
GO BABY.
GO GO.
I CAN'T SIT HERE ANYMORE.
>> HI GUYS IT'S ME IN THE SHOW. WE'RE AT
LUNCH TIME NOW.
>> WE'RE LEAVING CLASS.
>> WE'RE GOING TO EAT EVERYBODY UP.
>> FROM PACSUN AND THEN this is from
Off-White.
>> Period.
>> My jacket is from Ross. This is from
Fashion Nova and this is from Puma.
THIS IS MY SECOND DAY OF SCHOOL outfit
guys not my first day.
>> Okay guys this is from PLT. This is from
Missguided. This is from Tory.
>> Yeah guys.
>> PERIOD.
>> MY SHIRT IS FROM TIKTOK SHOP. THESE
pants are from Addicted. My shoes are
from Converse. My socks are green.
>> But yeah y'all that's really it for my
first day of senior year. That wraps up
today's video. Don't forget to follow me
on all my socials @mirertelme and as
always, I love you guys so much and God
loves you even more and goodbye.